

## Mohamed Y. Diab

+971 (0) 565630242 - MohamedYehiaDiab@gmail.com

Churchill Tower, Business Bay. Dubai

## **PROFILE**

A self-starter with a versatile mind set. With expansive experience in Customer Support. An innovative thinker with a strong mind for problem solving and sublime communication skills. With an established track record of increased customer satisfaction.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance

2015 - Current

## Customer service representative

- Handle complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits and follow up to ensure resolution.
- Identify and assess customers needs to achieve satisfaction.
- Build sustainable relationships of trust through open and interactive communication.
- Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods/tools.
- Go the extra mile to engage customers.
- Assist with placement of orders, refunds, or exchanges.
- Take payment information and other pertinent information such as addresses and phone numbers.

#### **Orange Telecommunications**

2011 - 2015

#### Customer service representative

Responsible for opening and maintaining customer accounts. Resolve product or service problems by clarifying the customer's complaint; determining the cause of the problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment; following up to ensure resolution.

Recommend potential products or services to management by collecting customer information and analyzing customer needs whilst providing products and service reports

## Contact Plus (Electronic Import)

2006 - 2010

## Co-Founder

Responsible for maintaining and growing the company client portfolio through different channels like Social media marketing, face to face networking. Whilst helping with developing the strategy necessary to improve the company business model and profits.

# **EDUCATION**

### **Advanced Academy**

Bachelor of Foreign Trade